CLAIRE TANG LAI PING

Born and raised in Hong Kong. Graduated from Wuhan University and currently in progress of a Master degree from City University of Hong Kong. Previous experience in Compliance Department with Intertrust Group and joined Westpac as Middle Office Analyst upon graduation.



tanglaipingclaire@outlook.com



+ 852 69991305



Immediately Available



Expected Salary: HKD 18,000

EDUCATION

Sep 2016 - Expected Summer 2017

City University of Hong Kong

Master of Science in Business Information Systems | GPA 3.60/4.30, distinction

Sep 2012 - July 2016 | Wuhan, China

Wuhan University

Bachelor of Arts in Business

Administration with a minor in English |

GPA 3.42/4.00, awarded three-year

scholarships

SKILLS

Relevant Coursework

Master:

Management Support and Business
Intelligence Systems (A) | Business
Software Construction (A-) |
Foundations of Information and
Electronic Business Systems (A-)

Undergrad:

Operational Research (99/100) |
Data Statistics Analysis Practice
(95/100) | Econometric Model
Experiment (93/100) | Statistics
(92/100) | Commercial
Communications and Negotiations
(92/100) |

Languages

English, Cantonese, Mandarin

Technical Skills

Excel | Visual Basic | Tableau | SAS | SPSS SQL | HTML | Adobe Illustrator

EXPERIENCE

Jan 2017 - Present | Hong Kong

Administrator, Regulatory Compliance | Intertrust Group

- Processing and calculating payments made by investors to bond to ensure timely bank balance, reporting, efficient cash transfers and adequate liquidity
- Reviewing and monitoring financial transactions, FATCA and CRS
- ◆ Conducting due diligence reviews on investors of bond, PE funds and hedge funds

Aug 2016 - Nov 2016 | Hong Kong

Analyst, Middle Office | Westpac Banking Corporation (Private Bank)

- ♦ Conducted due diligence reviews on PB clients' loans, transactions and FX records
- ♦ Conducted RP Data Property Profile Reports for the team
- ♦ Analyzed progress data on a weekly basis
- ♦ Extracted clients' data from Singapore hub and updated the client database

Apr 2016 - Aug 2016 | Hong Kong

Project Assistant, Compliance | Intertrust Group

- ◆ Joined as project assistant performing the duties of a Compliance Assistant
- ◆ Conducted reviews on suspected hits generated by system
- ♦ Communicated with business colleagues to ascertain compliance risks
- Updated the compliance system with analyses and decisions on processing hits
- ♦ Updated the client database for data maintenance and data integrity
- Provided assistance in the preparation of meeting agenda and minutes

Jan 2016 – Apr 2016 | Shenzhen, China

Co-founder | Shenzhen Zhongmi Network Technology Co., Ltd

- ◆ Conducted and analyzed the market research of domain names to identify the trend in the markets
- ◆ Analyzed options available for one client to sell his "applepay.cn" to Apple Pay
- ◆ Developed strategies for marketing to promote our brand and successfully received 1 million RMB investment from a renowned VC firm in Beijing

Feb 2015 - Jul 2015 | Wuhan, China

Established a business on my own at Wuhan University

A start-up with 3 million RMB angel investment organized by students in Peking University, Wuhan University and prestigious universities in China. I gave my independent designs to the Chief Executive of Hong Kong, when he came to visit WHU and my designs gained popularity in big newspaper interviews for quite some time. Sold 500+ clothes to professors, students and alumnus with promotional campaigns

CERTIFICATIONS

- ♦ Insurance Intermediaries Qualifying Examination Paper I, III, V | 2015
- ♦ 21st English Translation Competition in Hubei Province China | second prize | 2015
- ◆ 5 Columns published on "Wenhui Newspaper" during 2012-2013 sharing my study experiences in Mainland China with Hong Kong readers | 2012-2013